[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "100 - 1",
        "choices": [98, 97, 99, 96],
        "correct": 99
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "40 - 33",
        "choices": [2, 5, 7, 4],
        "correct": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "16 - 2",
        "choices": [6, 14, 12, 13],
        "correct": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "30 - 4",
        "choices": [26, 27, 24, 25],
        "correct": 27
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "20 - 5",
        "choices": [19, 16, 15, 20],
        "correct": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "10 - 10",
        "choices": [10, 0, 20, 25],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "70 - 14",
        "choices": [26, 96, 56, 43],
        "correct": 56
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "44 - 12",
        "choices": [32, 43, 50, 35],
        "correct": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "40 - 4",
        "choices": [36, 18, 40, 45],
        "correct": 35
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "28 - 2",
        "choices": [25, 26, 1, 43],
        "correct": 26
    }
]